Phi-Hai Nguyen full stack web developer

Phone:425-319-7872 | Email: phihai93@gmail.com | SEATTLE WA, 98146

PORTFOLIO: http://phihainguyen.github.io/Phi-Hai-Nguyen-Portfolio/index.html
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/phi-hai-nguyen | GitHub: https://github.com/phihainguyen

SUMMARY

Problem solver, with experience using the **MERN stack** (MongoDB, Express.js, React, Node.js), HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Sequelize and MySQL to build full-stack applications. Passionate about taking amazing ideas and transforming them into something aesthetically pleasing through coding.

SKILLS

FRONTEND: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, React

BACKEND: Node.js, Mongo DB, MySQL, NonSQL/Firebase

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Full Stack Web Developer, Seattle WA | April 2019 - Present

Live version of projects may be viewed here: http://phihainguyen.github.io/Phi-Hai-Nguyen-Portfolio/index.html

Socialweedia, Seattle WA | May 2019

WEB DESIGNER

Designed & Collaborated with Developing web-app using:

React, JavaScript, Axios & API, CSS, Bootstrap, Firebase, Cloudinary

Real Wize, Seattle WA | April 2019 UX DESIGNER/FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Cooperated with & Designed web-app using:

Handlebars, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, MySQL, AXIOS, AJAX, & APIs, Express.js

$\textbf{Washington State Department of Social and Health Services,} \ \textbf{Seattle WA | Sept 2014 - Present}$

HOME CARE AIDE

- Creating work schedule and constructing clients' personal care plans with client manager
- Contacting and updating client manager about client's condition and well being
- Creating solutions to client's daily tasks and problems which may occur

Our Lady of Lourdes Parish, Seattle WA | February 1999 - Present

CHOIR DIRECTOR/PIANIST/YOUTH LEADER

- Organizing and leading vocal ensembles during practice and church events
- Motivates and inspires choir and youth with positivity, strong leadership skills as well as being creative and firm
- Making sure members attend practice and are at their best when performing

Dr. Kenneth Nishimoto DDS, Burien WA | March 2018 - April 2019

DENTAL ASSISTANT

- Working well in a team by communicating clearly and effectively to patients, office members and Dentist about patients' treatment plan, concerns
- Conducting standup meetings about daily schedule, problems/obstacles faced during office hours, what needs to improve, how to improve and what went well
- Usage of Dentrix, a dental practice management software, for payroll, making/canceling/rescheduling patients' appointments, updating patients' and insurance information, and payment transactions

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY of WASHINGTON

CERTIFICATION in FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT | 2019

Intensive program aimed at learning the technical skills of being a Full Stack Web Developer, using the MERN stack

UNIVERSITY of WASHINGTON

BACHELOR of ARTS in BIOCHEMISTRY | 2013 - 2016